<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Flowtime-Zh</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="me">Me</string>
    <string name="start_meditation">Start</string>
    <string name="setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="help_center">Help Center</string>
    <string name="term_of_serivce">Terms of Services</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="minutes">min</string>
    <string name="wear_state">Wear State</string>
    <string name="wear_tip_content">Wear the headband and adjust the electrode contact as prompted</string>
    <string name="wear_state_left">The left</string>
    <string name="wear_state_right">The right</string>
    <string name="wear_state_normal">Connection Is Normal</string>

    <string name="brainwave_spectrum">Brainwave Spectrum</string>
    <string name="change_during_meditation">Changes During Meditation</string>
    <string name="about_brainwave">The change of the power ratio of the brainwaves reflects the change of mental state during meditation.</string>
    <string name="about_hrv">HRV changes with the state of meditation. The HRV is generally higher in the relaxed state. With long-term meditation practice, the overall level of HRV will increase.</string>
    <string name="about_hr">In general, the change of heart rate is disordered. Through long-term training, the heart rate can be seen in a certain periodic rhythm during meditation. At this time, the breathing and heartbeat reach a coordinated state.</string>
    <string name="about_relaxation_attention">If you do not have long-term meditation training, your brainwaves in a specific brain state is concentrated. When you are focused, the Relaxation value is generally low, and when you are relaxed, the Attention value is low. Attention and Relaxation are mutually exclusive. After long-term practice of meditation, brainwaves are spread more broadly and even. You can be relaxed and focused at the same time with a high score of both Attention and Relaxation. In this state, it is easier to have inspiration and creativity.</string>
    <string name="about_pressure">Deep breathing training can effectively reduce stress, and long-term meditation training can improve stress resilience. Pressure and relaxation graphs reflect your relaxation state on physical and phycological level.</string>
    <string name="brainwave">Brainwave</string>
    <string name="hrv">HRV</string>
    <string name="heart_rate">Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="realxation_and_attention">Relaxation&#038;Attention</string>
    <string name="pressure">Pressure</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn More</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>


    <string name="tip1_content">There are 3 different sizes of rubber bands. Please choose the band that fits closely to your head.</string>
    <string name="tip1_title">Tip 1</string>
    <string name="tip2_content">Adjust the headband so that the sensors fit snugly to the skin and the headband is in the middle of your forehead.</string>
    <string name="tip2_title">Tip 2</string>
    <string name="tip3_content">Please make sure there is no hair between the sensors and the skin.</string>
    <string name="tip3_title">Tip 3</string>
    <string name="tip4_content">When you speak or move eyes, these facial muscle activities will interfere in signal detection. If the signal is not stable, try to relax your face and eyes.</string>
    <string name="tip4_title">Tip 4</string>
    <string name="tip5_content">Skincare products, cosmetics, and sebum will prevent the sensors from detecting signals. Please clean the skin with a wet wipe to improve signal quality if needed.</string>
    <string name="tip5_title">Tip 5</string>
    <string name="tip6_content">Dry skin or dryness caused by the environment will affect signal detection. Please moisturize the skin with a wet wipe to improve signal quality if needed.</string>
    <string name="tip6_title">Tip 6</string>
    <string name="tip7_content">After each adjustment, it takes 30 seconds to 1 minute to detect the signals. Just relax and take a few breaths.</string>
    <string name="tip7_title">Tip 7</string>

    <string name="device_time_left">%1$d hours left</string>
    <string name="device_min_left">%1$d minutes left</string>
    <string name="activity_device_status_device_status">Device Status</string>
    <string name="activity_device_status_sensor_contact_check">Sensor Contact Check</string>
    <string name="activity_device_status_11">Wear the headband and adjust the sensor according to the illustration.</string>

    <string name="sensor_contact_check">Sensor Contact Check</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>

    <string name="checking">Checking...</string>
    <string name="well_done">Well done!</string>
    <string name="emotion">Emotion</string>

    <string name="min">min</string>
    <string name="second">s</string>
</resources>
